もう逃がさないわよ
You're not going anywhere!
Wait a second! I'm just...
ちょっと待ってくれ　俺は
Prepare to die!
勘弁しなさい
Misaka-san!
御坂さん
Oh.
Uiharu-san and Saten-san...
初春さん　佐天さん
何があったんですか
Did something just happen now?
I heard this really loud noise.
今なんかすごい音がしましたけど
え　いや　その　あハハハハ
Don't worry, it was just...
放て！心に刻んだ夢を
未来さえ置き去りにして
限界など知らない　意味無い！
この能力が光散らす　その先に遥かな想いを
チカラ
歩いてきた　この道を　振り返ることしか
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
暗闇に堕ちる街並み
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
加速するその痛みから
誰かをきっと守れるよ
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
身体中を　光の速さで　駆け巡った　確かな予感
掴め！望むものなら残さず　輝ける自分らしさで
信じてるよ　あの日の誓いを
この瞳に光る涙　それさえも強さになるから
今日は黒子とお姉様のアニバーサリー
Today is my anniversary with Onee-sama.
運命の赤い糸で結ばれて　ちょうど一ヶ月目の
It has been exactly one month since the red string of fate tied us together.
例の品物が届かなかったのは残念ですけど
It's too bad that the gift I ordered didn't arrive, but...
今日こそ黒子は差し上げますの
Today, I'll give her something even better.
A gift that comes from the bottom of my heart!
心を込めたプレゼント
そう　生まれたままの　この私よ
Yes! Me! As I was born!
ただい
I'm...
お姉様
Onee-sama!
back-
お邪魔 します
Sorry to bother-
わあ　憧れのお嬢様のお部屋
Oh, wow, so this is what an Ojou-sama's room looks like.
It's so stylish and chic.
おっしゃれ　シック
ベッドもふかふか
The bed is really soft too!
本当だ
Yeah, it is!
まったく　あんたは何考えてんるの
Geez, what's your problem?
This is great!
You should try it too, Uiharu!
You too! Why did you bring along Uiharu-san and Saten-san?
お姉様こそ　どうして初春と佐天さんを
たまたま街で会ったのよ　買い物にも付き合ってもらっちゃたし
Oh, I just happened to meet them while I was out in the city.
We went shopping together, and...
一度寮を見て見たいって言うから
they said they wanted to come see our dorm, so...
買い物
Shopping?
Eh?
ううん ちょっとね
Oh, I just...
The Tokiwadai dorms are as fabulous as I had imagined.
やっぱりすごいですね　常盤台の女子寮　羨ましいなぁ
I'm so jealous.
食堂なんかもこんな広かったもんね
The dining hall is huge, too!
そんなことないよ
Well, not really...
お姉様だっら　よりにもよってどうしてこの日に
Damn it! Why did Onee-sama have to bring them today, of all days!?
せっかくアニバーサリーが台無しですわ
Our anniversary is totally screwed up now!
あ　もしかしたら
Oh, it must be that...
Today is a very special day. It's been one month since Kuroko and I were bound together by the red string of fate!
私と黒子が運命の赤い糸で結ばれて　ちょうど一ヶ月の記念日なの
私と黒子は二人でひとつ
We're two halves of a whole.
初春さん 佐天さん これからも私たちをよろしくね
Uiharu-san, Saten-san, please take care of us.
君の瞳に　乾杯
Here's looking at you, kid.
あの　白井さん　大丈夫ですか
Umm... Shirai-san, are you okay?
何でもありませんの
Oh, it's nothing.
さあさあ　これといったおもてなしもできませんが
Now, now. We don't have much to offer you, but...
どうぞお好きにって
Please make yourselves comfortable-
Er...
佐天さん　そこで何を
What are you doing, Saten-san?
いや　友達の家にきたら　まずはお約束のがっさい例かなあって
Well, when you go over to a friend's house...
You're supposed to investigate, right?
あ　エロス
Oh ho! Erotic!
佐天さん　そんな人のもの勝手に
Saten-san! Don't invade other people's privacy!
さすが御坂さん　大人
Nice work, Misaka-san. Very adult.
いや　それは
No, that's...
私のですわ
It's mine!
白井さんの
This is Shirai-san's?
この大胆な下着が
This incredibly revealing one?
大胆というほどでも　黒の下着ぐらい　レディーの嗜みですわよ
It's not that revealing.
Black panties are a requirement for a proper lady.
This pair with the red butterfly, too?
じゃ このまっ赤のバタフライも
気持ちをもりあげたいときなど　その色を
I use that color when I'm feeling frisky.
このほとんど紐なティーバックも
And this stringy T-back?
お肌に跡が残れなくて重宝しますわ
That one is quite useful. It doesn't leave any marks on my skin.
この全身メッシュのボディーストキングーも
And these full body mesh stockings?
女には時としてめいひょうにならなければならないときがありますのよ
Sometimes a woman just has to become a panther.
いきなりなにするんですか　佐天さん
W-what are you doing, Saten-san!?
いや　なんか自分の日常を取り戻したくなって
Oh, you know, it's just my usual routine.
初春の縞パンみたら　落ち着いた
Seeing your striped panties always calms me down.
Why do you have to make such a big deal over underwear?
そんな下着ぐらいで大げさな
ほら　ほかにもいろいろありましてよ
Take a look. I have a lot more!
パール素材のオープンブライに振りるつきのベビー透る
A pearl textile open bra and a baby doll with frills.
ガーターベルトにレースのテディ
A garter belt and a lacy teddie.
And...
それから
What a relief.
よかった　白井さんもそんなの穿くんだ
So Shirai-san wears that kind too.
My Shirai-san has returned!
私の白井さんが帰ってきてくれました
ごめん　これ　私の
Sorry... These are mine...
えっ
つーか　黒子　なんであんたのベッドの下には私の下着があるんわけ
Wait a second, Kuroko!
Why is my underwear under your bed!
Huh?
It's a misunderstanding, Onee-sama!
まあまあ　御坂さん　そうだ　私　アルバムがみたいなあ
Calm down, Misaka-san...
Ooh, I want to see your photo albums!
Going for the basics, huh?
あ　定番だね
御坂さんと白井さんの小学校時代とか　すごい興味あります
I really want to see how you two looked in elementary school.
え
Eh..
わあ　可愛い
Oh, so cute!
これで　小学校の入学式ですか
Is this your elementary school entrance ceremony?
隣のきれいな人　お母さんですか
Is that beautiful person next to you your mother?
Um... yes...
あ うん
着物
What a nice kimono.
懐かしいね　これ
This is embarrassing...
でも　ちょっと意外
I have to say, though, this is kind of unexpected.
なにが
What is?
<Level 5>
ほら　御坂さんで　超能力者で
Well, Misaka-san, you're a Level 5 and the ace of Tokiwadai.
常盤台のエースじゃないですか
なんかいい所のお嬢様で
I would have figured that you were from an upper-class family.
子供のごろからエリートガイドまっしぐらみたいなあ
You know, someone who's been walking the path of the elite their entire life.
そんなことないよ
Oh, that's not it at all.
<Level 1>
私だって 最初は低能力者だったし
I started out as a Level 1. I was just a normal kid.
全然普通の子だったって
へい
I see...
じゃ 次は白井さんの
Let's look at Shirai-san's next.
ええ　喜んで
Oh, I would love to...
と申したいところですが　あいにく私アルバムが持ち合わせておりませんの
Unfortunately, I don't have a photo album.
あ
Huh?
黒子は今を生きる女　過去を振りかえるよりも　未来を夢みるよりも
I live in the present.
Instead of dwelling in the past or dreaming of the future,
いまを　いまこの瞬間を見つめていたい
I want to live in the present.
そう心に決めておりますのよ
That's something I've promised myself.
Isn't it this?
これじゃん
AAAAAGH!
いや それはだめですの
That isn't allowed!
Oh my...
黒子
Kuroko!
確かに　あんたは過去や未来より
You should be reflecting on the present, not the past or the future!
いまこの瞬間を見つめなおす必要があるわね
I'm just that serious about you, Onee-sama!
私それだけ本気でお姉様のこと
お姉様　今日がなんの日か覚えていらっしゃいませんの
Don't you remember what today is?
初春や佐天さんをつれていらっしたとも　てっきりこの日のためだとばかり
I thought you brought Uiharu-san and Saten-san here because of that...
Today?
今日 初春さんと佐天さん
Uiharu-san and Saten-san...
あ そういえば
Oh, come to think of it...
思いだしてくださいまして
You remember now?
きょうは初春さん　佐天さんと知り合って
Yeah. This is a very important day. It's been a week since I met Uiharu-san and Saten-san.
ちょうど一週間目の記念日だ
早いもので　あれからもう一週間だったんですね
Time sure flies. It's already been a week...
って言うかまだ一週間なんだ
Well, I guess it's more like it's only been a week, huh?
なんかもうずっと前から一緒にいるような気になってました
It sure feels like we've been together forever.
これからもよろしくね
Let's keep sticking together, okay?
なんなんですの　この扱いの差は
Why does she treat them so much better than me!?
黒子ひょっとしていらない子
Am I unnecessary!?
この小豆　誰にもかえりみられずに捨てられる
This Azuki bean...
No one notices you. They just throw you out.
この孤独の小豆と同じですの
I'm just like this poor little Azuki bean!
これ意外にいけるよ
Hey, this is great!
えっ　カクサイト
Oh. wow!
Pork cutlet sandwiches?
And after that, Uiharu...
そしたらその後　初春が
ちょっと　佐天さん
Hey, Saten-san!
That's horrible!
これひどい
うるさいわね　あんだは　先から
Pipe down, will ya?
妬けじる子ですわ
I'm drowning my sorrows in Shiruko.
は
Huh?
How I could not be!?
これが妬けにならずにいられましょうか
えっと
Um...
All this after only a week!
出会って一週間 笑わせないでくださいな
Don't make me laugh!
一ヶ月
A month...
今日はお姉様と私が運命の赤い糸で結ばれてちょうど一ヶ月目の記念日ですのよ
It has been exactly one month since the red string of fate tied us together!
一月前のこの日　黒子とお姉様は偶然にもこの部屋のルームメートになった
One month ago, on this same day,
we ended up becoming roommates by coincidence.
以来　寝食をともにし　喜びも悲しみも分かちあってきて
We've eaten and slept together since then.
We've even shared in each other's triumphs and defeats.
Right here! Right here in this room!
ここで　この部屋で
Yet, yet... Onee-sama, you...
なのに　なのに　お姉様だっら
白井さん
Shirai-san...
あたしたち　およびじゃなかったかな
Maybe we aren't welcome...
黒子　あんだ
Kuroko...
You...
お姉様
Onee-sama?
You barged in here, didn't you?
無理やりここに押しかけてきたよね
偶然でも　運命の赤い糸でもなくさ　それでなに
It wasn't a coincidence. Or the red string of fate.
And what are you going on about?
喜び　悲しみ　やけじるこ
Happiness? Sorrow?
Um, I have some business to attend to...
私何から急用
Drowning your sorrows in Shiruko?
Stop making crap up!
よくもそこまでいったわね
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
It's a difference of opinion!
変態　掃除
That's right! Perversion must be stamped out!
そうよね　変態は掃除しちゃわないとね
見解の相違ですの
No, I said it was a difference of opinion.
それに私はただ　お姉様と今日という日をささやかにお祝いした
And I just...
I just wanted to celebrate this day quietly.
Hello?
はい
宅急便です　２０８号室　白井黒子さんの部屋でよろしいでしょうか
This is FedEx.
Is this room 208, Shirai Kuroko-san's room?
はい　あの　品物は
Yes.
And... What are the contents?
パソコン部品とありますが
They're labeled as PC parts.
Of course.
そりゃそうですわね　あの店の業者はそのあたりよく心得ってますもの
Those guys really know what's going on.
お送り主は
Who sent it?
有限会社　愛と漢方の絶倫媚薬さまからです
Love and Chinese Traditional Hypersexual Love Potions, LTD.
Damn, they should have hidden that part!
そこ明記してどうしますの
黒子　ささやかにお祝いはするのに何で媚薬がいるのかしら
Kuroko, why do you need a love potion for a "quiet celebration?"
Um...
えっと
It looks like drastic measures will be required to stamp out your perversion.
あんだの変態性質を直すには　相当な荒量子が必要なようね
I'm gonna zap you into charcoal!
ここでその名の通り　　真っ黒焦げになりなさい
O-Onee-sama...
おははは　私の能力をお忘れになっては困りますわ
You mustn't forget my ability.
We have no choice but to eat or be eaten!
こうなったら食うか食われるか　黒子の愛を受け入れられないのなら
If you can't accept my love,
いっそう　黒子と戦ってくださいまし
then please duel me!
お姉様
Onee-sama?
寮則第九条　寮内での能力の使用はこれを硬く禁んずる
Dormitory Law, code 9,
The use of abilities inside of the dormitory is absolutely prohibited.
よもや忘れたわけではあるまい　白井さん
You can't have forgotten, Shirai.
Hmm?
ここここれはご機嫌麗しゅう　舎監官さま
O-oh, good afternoon, dormitory supervisor.
もちろんですわ
Of course I haven't.
私たち　ただいたずらに能力を使ったわけではありませんの
No, we weren't just using our abilities haphazardly...
これにはいろいろと深い訳
We had a very good reason...
なるほど　よんとごろない事情というやつか
I see.
Unavoidable circumstances, you could say?
そうなんですの　実は
T-that's right!
Actually...
だが
But...
K-Kuroko
黒子
I cannot protect the law and order of the dormitority if I take "unavoidable circumstances" into account.
そんな事情一々斟酌していては　寮の規律を守ることはできん
規則破りには罰が必要だ　そうは思わんか　御坂
Those who break the rules must be punished.
Don't you agree, Misaka?
Y-yes.
#2 You need to stay hydrated
if you work under the sun
A Certain Scientific Railgun
はい
たっくもう なんで私がこんなことを
Geez... Why do I have to do this?
確かにちょうっとやり過ぎだけど
I mean, I may have overdone it a little, but...
だからで　その罰が
I can't believe that the penalty for that is...
Cleaning this huge freakin' pool!
このくそ広いプール掃除って
いくらなんでもそれりゃ無理でしょう
Seriously, of all the things they could have had us do! This is impossible!
朝からやって　もう昼過ぎだってのに
We've been doing this since morning! It's already past noon!
まだ三割も終わってないって　どう言うこと
How can we not have finished even a third of it?
これ今日中終わんのかしらね
Are we going to be able to finish this today?
これはラッキーですわ
I'm lucky.
水場で汗だくな濡れ濡れのお姉様と二人きりのプライベートタイム
Being with a sweaty, dripping Onee-sama at the pool...
Private time for just the two of us.
まさに昨日の雪辱を晴らす　千載一遇のチャンスですのよ
This is a once in a million chance to make up for yesterday's failure!
お姉様
Onee-sama,
Huh?
You need to stay hydrated when you work under the sun.
炎天下の作業には水分補給が必須ですのよ
私の特製のドリンキングはいかが
Why don't you try this special drink of mine?
要らない
No need.
W-why not?
どうしてですの
You haven't poured your "PC parts" into that drink, have you?
あんた　昨日のパソコン部品
まさかその中に入れたりしてないわね
やっぱりか
As I thought.
白井さん
Shirai-san?
Oh, it's Shirai-san.
やっぱり白井さんですわ
こんなところで何をなさってますの
What are you doing here?
見ての通り　プール掃除ですわ
As you can see,
we're cleaning the pool.
でも　どうして
But why?
初夏でも　世間の風が冷たいですの
It may be summer right now, but the cold wind of society continues to blow.
そう言う　あなた達は
And what about you two?
私たちは水泳部員ですので
Well, we're on the swim team, so...
黒子のクラスメイトか
Kuroko's classmates.
ってことは
That means...
年下か
They're younger than me...
お姉様　こちらは私のクラスメイトの
Onee-sama,
these are my classmates,
湾内絹保さんと泡浮万彬さんですの
Wannai Kinuho-san and Awatsuki Maaya-san.
こんにちは
Good afternoon.
ってこちらが
And this is...
Please excuse me, but would you be Misaka-sama?
あの　失礼ですが　御坂様でして
えぇ　そうだけど
Oh?
Well, I am, but...
やっぱり
So you are!
覚えてらっしゃいませんか
Do you not remember me?
私　せんだて粗暴なとな方に取り囲まれておりましたところを
You saved me from some very violent men once.
御坂様に助ていただいて
あぁ　そんなこともあったっけ
Oh, I think I remember that...
その節は　本当にお世話になりました
I'm very grateful that you saved me.
お噂は兼ね兼ね　お会えできて光栄ですわ
I've heard a lot of great things about you.
I'm delighted to be able to meet you.
さすかはお姉様　私の知らないところでも悪者を懲らしめてらっしゃいますのね
Well, that's just how Onee-sama rolls.
She's always off punishing bad guys, even when I'm not around.
その方が怖くって
But men are so scary...
本当に　暖かくなると変なの増えるしね
But, yeah, really...
All the weirdos come out when it gets warm!
でも　さすかですわ
You really are awesome!
本当にあの時の御坂様は素敵でした
Yeah, you were so totally cool back then!
いえいえいえ　　雑用って感じね
Oh, it was nothing.
This is...?
これは　デジャブ　気のせいですわ
That's so cruel.
Deja vu!?
No, it's just my imagination!
昨日の今日でナーバスになているだけ
I'm just on edge because of what happened yesterday!
黒子だけ仲間外れにされるなんでそんなこと
There's no way I'm the only one not being included again!
この熱い中　大変でしょう
It must be tough, working under the sun like this.
スポーツドリンキングを持参しておりますので
I have a sports drink with me...
よろしかったら
If you would like some...
ありがとう　いただくわ
Oh, thank you.
I'll take it.
NO WAY!
Why is she treating them so much better than me!?
何なんですの　この扱いの差は
そう言えば
Come to think of it...
これまで　断るごとにするんされ来ましたし
She always tries to ignore me, no matter the situation.
こりに触れて親睦を深めようとしても　手荒く拒絶されて来ましたの
And, whenever I take steps to strengthen our relationship,
she rejects me flat-out.
お姉様　ひょっとして私のこと　本気で疎んじてらっしゃる
Is Onee-sama seriously avoiding me?
しっかりするのよ　黒子
Stay strong, Kuroko!
自信がないなら　取り戻すまで
If you lack confidence, you just need to find some!
不安があるなら　吹き飛ばすまで
If something is worrying you, then just blow it away!
<Teleport>
そう　私だけのアドバンテージ空間移動能力を持てすれば
Yes, something only I can do...
I can help Onee-sama in countless ways with my teleportation ability!
お姉様のお役に立つことなど　いくらでも
わぁ　すごい　見る見るきれいなってく
Oh, awesome!
You're cleaning it so quickly!
私の能力　水流操作系なんです
I have the ability to control the flow of water.
点検簿を先生に提出しなければならないんですけど
I need to hand in a report about the equipment.
それが済んだら　お手伝いをさせていただけませんか
Can I help you after I'm done with that?
Oh, but...
えぇ　でも
助けていただいた　せめてのお礼ですわ
I just want to repay you for saving me in some way.
ありがとう　すごく助かるわ
Thank you!
You'll be a great help!
喜んでいただいて嬉しいです
I'm glad I can help.
でも本当すごいね　これならあっという間だよ
You really are awesome...
We'll finish in no time with your help!
ありがとうございます
Thank you!
それでは　また後ほど
See you later, then.
スポーツドリンキング　ここに置いておきますので
I'll leave the drinks here, so feel free to help yourself.
ご自由にどうぞ
They're nice kids, huh, Kuroko?
なんかいい子たちじゃない　黒子
そうですわね
Certainly.
有り難いわね　あれなら十分かかないかも
They're so helpful.
She might be able to get it done in less than ten minutes.
そうですわね
Certainly.
あぁ　早く終わらせてアイス食べたい
I wanna get this over and eat some ice cream.
そうですわね
Certainly.
ん 十世紀に誕生した中国の王朝と言えば
What's the Chinese dynasty that came into being in the 10th century?
そうですわね
Sou.
どうしたの　元気ないわね
What's with you?
You don't seem very lively.
いいえ　お構いなく
It's nothing. Please don't mind me.
私なんて　掃除もろくにこなせない能無しですから
I'm so useless. I can't even clean.
えと　何か悩み事があるなら
If something is worrying you...
結構ですの
No need!
I'm not worthy of being in Onee-sama's presence.
私がお姉様に相応しくないのがいけないです
迷惑ばかりをかけして　お役にも立てない
All I do is cause you trouble. I can't help you at all.
こんな私ではお姉様のお傍にいる資格がありませんの
Someone like me doesn't deserve to be by your side!
What am I supposed do?
どう　どうしよう
行き成り過ぎで　付いていけないですけど
I can't understand you... this is so sudden...
御坂さん　もう渡しましたかね
I wonder if Misaka-san gave it to her?
どうせいなら渡しとこ見たかったね
Well, we should have seen her doing it.
せっがく買い物に付き合ったんだから
I mean, we did go shopping with her.
白井さんの反応が気になります
I want to see how Shirai-san reacts.
ほら　あの下着の趣味といい
Her choice of underwear was pretty...
そうなんだよな　まさがあんな趣味だと思わなかったから
That's right.
I didn't think she liked stuff like that.
でもほら　ああ言うのは気持ちだから
Oh well. It's the thought that counts, right?
そうですね
Yeah.
ねぇ　黒子
Hey, Kuroko?
一月前の今日のこと　覚えてる
Do you remember about this day, a month ago?
一月前の今日
This day, a month ago?
そう　あんだが私の部屋に押しかけて来た夜
Yes.
You barged into my room that night,
寮監に見つかて大目玉食らったでしょう
and the dormitory supervisor found you and punished us, right?
って　次の日　二人で食堂の掃除させられて
And we were forced to clean the dining hall the next day...
って　結局なんだかんだで　今日まで一緒にやって来た
We've managed to stick together through thick and thin since then, huh?
私たちに記念日があるとしたら　それって今日なんじゃないかな
I think that today...
is a very special day for us.
Oh...
Here.
C-can I open it?
あ　開けて見ても
もちろん
Sure!
これからもずっと一緒なんだから　よろしく頼むわよ
Looks like we're gonna be together forever after this, so...
Here's to you, Kuroko.
Oneesama, did you just say we'd be together forever?
お　お姉様今ずっと一緒って
当たり前でしょう
Of course.
同じ学校の同じ部屋で暮らす
We're inseparable partners. We live in the same room and go to the same school.
離れようにも離れられない　パートナーなんだからさ
はい　パートナーに　乾杯
Here...
Three cheers for being partners!
Partners tied by the red string of fate!
--運命の赤い糸と言う意味で　--ルームメートと言う意味で
Partners who are roommates.
さてっと　また一著頑張るか
Okay, let's get back to work.
お姉様
Onee-sama...
Onee-sama
プールのお掃除はぬれても平気な水着の方がよろしくなって
Shouldn't you wear a swimsuit while working in the pool, in case you get wet?
Huh?
でも　まぁ　取りに行くのも面倒だしね
Well, I didn't want to go to the trouble of finding one...
実はこんなこともあろうかと
Not to worry...
ジャンジャン　お姉様のスクール水着もちゃんと持て来ってますのよ
Look!
I have your school swimsuit with me!
鍵付きのロッカーに入れて置いたはずなんだけどね
I thought I had it locked up!
私の能力の前では鍵など無意味ですのよ
Locks mean nothing to me.
さぁさぁ　お召しになってくださいまし
Now, now, please put it on.
えぇ
Huh?
お姉様ったら　またこんな子供っぽいものを
Onee-sama, your swimsuit is so childish.
Kuroko! Give them back!
こら　返せ
ですから水着を
Like I said, swimsuits...
あら　あらあら　お揃　お揃ですわ
Oh...
Oh my, these two are a pair!
A pair!
お揃　お揃　お姉様とお揃
A pair with Onee-sama!
Kuroko!
黒子
なんだか賑やかですわね
Looks like they're having fun.
御坂様　点検が終わりましたので　お手伝いを
Misaka-sama, I'm finished, so I came to help.
いい　お姉様の愛の鞭　とてもいいわ　わぉ
Onee-sama's loving beating! So wonderful!
Just give it back to me!
いいから　返せ　返しなさいよ
I'm telling you... to give it back!
いやですよ
I won't.
返すと言ってんのよ
Ecstasy!
この快感
また言うか
You're still talking about that?
Give it back! Give it back, damn it!
見　見なかったことにしましょう
We didn't see anything...
Give it back, damn it!
Yes...
そう　そうですね
黒子はくちけませんの
Kuroko won't lose.
ずっとお姉様のお傍にいますのよ
I will be beside Onee-sama forever.
Dear My Friend Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear My Friend every day & night
話しても　まだまだ　足りないまま
夕焼けが　街を染めてゆく
思うように　なかなか　いかない…って
気づいたら　一緒に　泣いていた
恋も　夢も　花も　虹も　風も
ぜんぶ掴もうよ
ダイジョウブ！　元気出して
私がそばにいるから
今日のミス　悔やむより　今　乗り越えて
ダイジョウブ！　迷わないで
まだ見ぬ未来へと向かって
ずっと　歩いてゆこう
Dear My Friend every day & night
Always be with you
Next Episode
Love...
Hate...
えぇ
Tokiwadai
Under
Fire
Love...
ちょっと　あの
Huh? Um...
Hate...
Shirai-san, don't use the flowers on my head to predict how your relationships will go!
白井さん私の頭の花で恋花占いするのやめてください
Love...
Hate...